Guide to the Medical Center records, 1825-2005 RG0007
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Personnel files, circa 1970-circa 1989; RG0007 Series 1; 34.5 Linear feet
  - Manitsas, Hildegard, undated (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Mann, James, undated (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Mann, Oscar, undated (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Marans, Alien E., undated (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Margileth, Andrew, undated (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Markwood, Emmett, undated (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Marland, Albert, undated (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Marsh, William, undated (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Martel, Leon, undated (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Martin, Robert, undated (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Martin, Shirley Sue, undated (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Martyn, Herbert, undated (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Massumi, Rashid, undated (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Mastellone, Aniello, undated (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Mastrota, Francis, undated (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Mate Jr., Frank, undated (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - McAllister, Harry, undated (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - Mcateer, Gerald, undated (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - McAvoy, William, undated (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - McCann, Harold F., undated (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - McCarthy, Joseph, undated (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - McCarty, Dennis, undated (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - McCeney, Robert, undated (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - McClelland, James, undated (Box 11, Folder 73)
  - McClenathan, James E., undated (Box 11, Folder 74)
  - McCollum, Donald, undated (Box 11, Folder 75)
  - McCune, William, undated (Box 11, Folder 76)
  - McDonald, Joseph, undated (Box 11, Folder 77)
  - McDonald, Audrey, undated (Box 11, Folder 78)
  - McFall, Creed, undated (Box 11, Folder 79)
  - McFarland, James, undated (Box 11, Folder 80)
  - McGavin, Thomas, undated (Box 11, Folder 81)
  - McGrath, Robert, undated (Box 11, Folder 82)
  - McKee, Thistle, undated (Box 11, Folder 83)
  - McKelvie, Allan, undated (Box 11, Folder 84)
  - McKelvie, Allan, undated (Box 11, Folder 85)
  - McLain, George, undated (Box 11, Folder 86)
  - McLendon, Preston, undated (Box 11, Folder 87)
  - McMahon, Thomas, undated (Box 11, Folder 88)
  - McNamara, C. Edwin, undated (Box 11, Folder 89)
  - McNitt, Arnold McNutt, Agnes, undated (Box 11, Folder 90)
  - Mctigue, John, undated (Box 11, Folder 91)
  - Mead, Sterling G., undated (Box 11, Folder 92)
  - Mead, Sterling V., undated (Box 11, Folder 93)
  - Meiman, William G., undated (Box 11, Folder 94)
  - Mendelsohn, Robert, undated (Box 11, Folder 95)
  - Mendelson, Wallace, undated (Box 11, Folder 96)
  - Mensh, Maurice, undated (Box 11, Folder 97)
  - Metzger, Arthur, undated (Box 11, Folder 98)
  - Meyersburg, Herman, undated (Box 11, Folder 99)
  - Mezitia, Fofo, undated (Box 11, Folder 100)
  - Michael, Morris, undated (Box 11, Folder 101)
  - Miller, Beveridge, undated (Box 11, Folder 102)
  - Miller, Philip, undated (Box 11, Folder 103)
  - Miller, Bretney, undated (Box 11, Folder 104)
  - Miller, Joseph, undated (Box 11, Folder 105)
  - Miller, Frank, undated (Box 11, Folder 106)
  - Miller, William, undated (Box 11, Folder 107)
  - Millwater, Charles, undated (Box 11, Folder 108)
  - Milstead, Valgene, undated (Box 11, Folder 109)
  - Min, Frances WhaShik, undated (Box 11, Folder 110)
  - Mincosky, Abraham Burton, undated (Box 11, Folder 111)
  - Mishtowt, George, undated (Box 11, Folder 112)
  - Mitchell, Earl, undated (Box 11, Folder 113)
  - Mitchell, Robert, undated (Box 11, Folder 114)
  - Monat, Henry, undated (Box 11, Folder 115)
  - Mones, Marvin, undated (Box 11, Folder 116)
  - Moneymaker, Thomas, undated (Box 11, Folder 117)
  - Montgomery, Robert, undated (Box 11, Folder 118)
  - Moody, Louis Henry, undated (Box 11, Folder 119)
  - Morette, Frederic, undated (Box 11, Folder 120)
  - Moretti, Frederic A., undated (Box 11, Folder 121)
  - Morris, Arthur, undated (Box 11, Folder 122)
  - Morris, John, undated (Box 11, Folder 123)
  - Morris, Oriel, undated (Box 11, Folder 124)
  - Mortell, Edward, undated (Box 11, Folder 125)
  - Moser, James M., Jr., undated (Box 11, Folder 126)
  - Moses, William R., undated (Box 11, Folder 127)
  - Moss, James M., undated (Box 11, Folder 128)
  - Mott, Howard, undated (Box 11, Folder 129)
  - Moulton, Barbara, undated (Box 11, Folder 130)
  - Mourad, Mahmoud, undated (Box 11, Folder 131)
  - Mourot, Arthur, undated (Box 11, Folder 132)
  - Mugmon, Leo, undated (Box 11, Folder 133)
  - Muilenburg, Robert, undated (Box 11, Folder 134)
  - Mundell, Benjamin, undated (Box 11, Folder 135)
  - Murphy Jr., Christopher J., undated (Box 11, Folder 136)
  - Murphy, James, undated (Box 11, Folder 137)
  - Murphy, Cornelius F., undated (Box 11, Folder 138)
  - Murphy, Frank J., undated (Box 11, Folder 139)
  - Murphy, Thomas W., undated (Box 11, Folder 140)
  - Myers, Henry J., undated (Box 11, Folder 141)
  - FILE "N", undated (Box 11, Folder 142)
  - Naccash, Edmund, undated (Box 11, Folder 143)
  - Nachlas, Arthur, undated (Box 11, Folder 144)
  - Namrow, Arnold, undated (Box 11, Folder 145)
  - Naser, Auron, undated (Box 11, Folder 146)
  - Neslen, Earl, undated (Box 11, Folder 147)
  - Nessell, William Edward, undated (Box 11, Folder 148)
  - Neu, Robert, undated (Box 11, Folder 149)
  - Nolan, John, undated (Box 11, Folder 150)
  - Norcross, John, undated (Box 11, Folder 151)
  - Normyle, John, undated (Box 11, Folder 152)
  - Nugent, James, undated (Box 11, Folder 153)
  - Nunez, Bernard, undated (Box 11, Folder 154)
  - Nails, Walter, undated (Box 11, Folder 155)
  - Naples, Carmon, undated (Box 11, Folder 156)
  - Nathanson, Esther A., undated (Box 11, Folder 157)
  - Nathanson, Leon Irving, undated (Box 11, Folder 158)
  - Nealon, Stephen, undated (Box 11, Folder 159)
  - Nelson, Robert B., Jr., undated (Box 11, Folder 160)
  - Nelson, Warren, undated (Box 11, Folder 161)
  - Nesbitt, John, undated (Box 11, Folder 162)
  - Nestor, John O., undated (Box 11, Folder 163)
  - Neumann, Anna, undated (Box 11, Folder 164)
  - Neviaser, Julius S., undated (Box 11, Folder 165)
  - Newman, Emanue1, undated (Box 11, Folder 166)
  - Newman, William, undated (Box 11, Folder 167)
  - Ney, Joseph, undated (Box 11, Folder 168)
  - Nicholson, Margaret, undated (Box 11, Folder 169)
  - Nicholson, Charles, undated (Box 11, Folder 170)
  - Nicklas, Edward, undated (Box 11, Folder 171)
  - Nimetz, Aaron, undated (Box 11, Folder 172)
  - Nimetz, Blanche, undated (Box 11, Folder 173)
  - Nobel, Douglas, undated (Box 11, Folder 174)
  - Nolan, James Edward, undated (Box 11, Folder 175)
  - Nolan, David, undated (Box 11, Folder 176)
  - Nordlinger, George, undated (Box 11, Folder 177)
  - Normyle, John, undated (Box 11, Folder 178)
  - O'Brien, Helen, undated (Box 11, Folder 179)
  - O'Donnell, Robert, undated (Box 11, Folder 180)
  - O'Donnell, Paul, undated (Box 11, Folder 181)
  - O'Lansky, Sidney, undated (Box 11, Folder 182)
  - Oleinick, Arthur, undated (Box 11, Folder 183)
  - Olinick, Stanley, undated (Box 11, Folder 184)
  - Olson, Ralph, undated (Box 11, Folder 185)
  - Ong, Harry, undated (Box 11, Folder 186)
  - Orr, William, undated (Box 11, Folder 187)
  - Orvis, Harold, undated (Box 11, Folder 188)
  - O'Brien, John R., undated (Box 11, Folder 189)
  - O'Brien, John F., undated (Box 11, Folder 190)
  - O'Donnell, Vincent, undated (Box 11, Folder 191)
  - O'Reilly, Sean, undated (Box 11, Folder 192)
  - Odenwald, Robert, undated (Box 11, Folder 193)
  - Ohaneson, Edward, undated (Box 11, Folder 194)
  - Oldham, William, undated (Box 11, Folder 195)
  - Olds, Corwin, undated (Box 11, Folder 196)
  - Oler, Wesley, undated (Box 11, Folder 197)
  - Orlosky, Albert, undated (Box 11, Folder 198)
  - Ormandy, Laszlo, undated (Box 11, Folder 199)
  - Ostrow, Bernard, undated (Box 11, Folder 200)
  - Owen, Robert, undated (Box 11, Folder 201)
  - Imburg, Jerome, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Itscoitz, Seymour, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Inguagiato, Gerald, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Iovine, Vincent, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Irani, ardeshir, undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Irey, Hugh, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Jackson, Donald, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Jacobson, Avrohm, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - James, Reginald, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Jamison, Benjamin, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Johnson, David, undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Johnson, Catherine, undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Johnson, Linwood, undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Jackson, Alfred Edison, undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Jackson, Caroline, undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Jacobs, Robert, undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Jaeger, Henry, undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Jaffe, Daniel, undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Jaffe, Vita, undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Jansa, Milos, undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Jansen, Russell, undated (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Jarobe, James, undated (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Jarman, W. Dabney, undated (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Jarvis, Garth, undated (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Jenkins, William, undated (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Jensen, Wallace, undated (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Johnson, Donald, undated (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Johnson, John, undated (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Jones, Ben, undated (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Jones, Charles, undated (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Jorgensen, Orlin, undated (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Kagan, Harold, undated (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Kaibni, Fuad, undated (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Kapiloff, Bernard, undated (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Kaplan, Naomi, undated (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Katzman, Howard, undated (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Kaufman, Harry, undated (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Kaufman, Paul, undated (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Kehne, Christine, undated (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Kelley, James, undated (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Kellow, William, undated (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Kelly, Alex, undated (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Kelly Jr., Timothy, undated (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Kerr, Harry, undated (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Kessler, Edwin, undated (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Khaury, Assad, undated (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Killay, W. H., undated (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Kinchelle, Charles, undated (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Kirchick, Julian, undated (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Klopfenstein, Karl, undated (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Kolb, Karl, undated (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Kolb, Lawrence, undated (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Kolkin, Marvin, undated (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Krebser, Werner, undated (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Kahler, Elizabeth, undated (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Kailin, Eloise, undated (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Kaiser, Paula, undated (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Kanof, Naomi, undated (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - Katzen, Bernard, undated (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Kaufman, Julius, undated (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Kaufman, Morton, undated (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Kay, Alvin, undated (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - Keaveny, John Francis, undated (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Keck, Charles, undated (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - Keeney, Dan, undated (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - Kehne, Wilmer, undated (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - Keliher, Thomas, undated (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - Kelly, Timothy, undated (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - Reiser, George, undated (Box 12, Folder 69)
  - Kendrick, Marvin, undated (Box 12, Folder 70)
  - Kenealy, John, undated (Box 12, Folder 71)
  - Kenmore, Peter, undated (Box 12, Folder 72)
  - Kepler, Milton, undated (Box 12, Folder 73)
  - Kessler, Israel, undated (Box 12, Folder 74)
  - Kiherer, Harry, undated (Box 12, Folder 75)
  - Kiernan, Paul, undated (Box 12, Folder 76)
  - Kiessling, Alice, undated (Box 12, Folder 77)
  - Kimble, Seruch, undated (Box 12, Folder 78)
  - King, Allan, undated (Box 12, Folder 79)
  - King, Clapham, undated (Box 12, Folder 80)
  - King, John, undated (Box 12, Folder 81)
  - King, Joseph, undated (Box 12, Folder 82)
  - Kinsbergan, Maurice, undated (Box 12, Folder 83)
  - Kirstein, Stanley, undated (Box 12, Folder 84)
  - Kistin, Albert, undated (Box 12, Folder 85)
  - Kleh, Jack, undated (Box 12, Folder 86)
  - Klein, Lewis, undated (Box 12, Folder 87)
  - Kleinerman, Morris, undated (Box 12, Folder 88)
  - Klepser, Roy, undated (Box 12, Folder 89)
  - Klopp, Calvin, undated (Box 12, Folder 90)
  - Kneipp, John, undated (Box 12, Folder 91)
  - Knop, Catharine, undated (Box 12, Folder 92)
  - Koppel, Albert, undated (Box 12, Folder 93)
  - Kramm, August, undated (Box 12, Folder 94)
  - Kreglow, Alan, undated (Box 12, Folder 95)
  - Kress, Scheldon, undated (Box 12, Folder 96)
  - Kreuzburg, Harvey, undated (Box 12, Folder 97)
  - Krichmar, Robert, undated (Box 12, Folder 98)
  - Krick, Jerome, undated (Box 12, Folder 99)
  - Kuhn, Amy, undated (Box 12, Folder 100)
  - Kurtz, C. Roger, undated (Box 12, Folder 101)
  - Kurtz, James, undated (Box 12, Folder 102)
  - Kushner, David, undated (Box 12, Folder 103)
  - Lambert, William, undated (Box 12, Folder 104)
  - Lambros, Vasilios, undated (Box 12, Folder 105)
  - Leary, Patrick, undated (Box 12, Folder 106)
  - Lederer, Ludwig, undated (Box 12, Folder 107)
  - Leigh Jr., Randolph, undated (Box 12, Folder 108)
  - Lepper, Mark, undated (Box 12, Folder 109)
  - Leva, Shirley, undated (Box 12, Folder 110)
  - Lewis, Lloyd, undated (Box 12, Folder 111)
  - Litvin, Philip, undated (Box 12, Folder 112)
  - Lloyd, John, undated (Box 12, Folder 113)
  - Logan, John, undated (Box 12, Folder 114)
  - Lombard, Peter, undated (Box 12, Folder 115)
  - Ludwig, Bernard, undated (Box 12, Folder 116)
  - Lady, William, undated (Box 12, Folder 117)
  - Lafsky, Benjamin, undated (Box 12, Folder 118)
  - Landman, Manuel, undated (Box 12, Folder 119)
  - Lane, Herbert E., Jr., undated (Box 12, Folder 120)
  - Latimer, John W., Jr., undated (Box 12, Folder 121)
  - Laughlin, Henry P., undated (Box 12, Folder 122)
  - Lavine, Oscar, undated (Box 12, Folder 123)
  - Law, Charles, undated (Box 12, Folder 124)
  - Lechaux, Pierre, undated (Box 12, Folder 125)
  - Lee, Allan, undated (Box 12, Folder 126)
  - Lee, Robert, undated (Box 12, Folder 127)
  - Leeper,Donald, undated (Box 12, Folder 128)
  - Lehrman, Harold, undated (Box 12, Folder 129)
  - Lemeshewsky, George, undated (Box 12, Folder 130)
  - Lenhoff, Charles, undated (Box 12, Folder 131)
  - Lenz, Paul, undated (Box 12, Folder 132)
  - Leonard, Thomas, undated (Box 12, Folder 133)
  - Leventhal, Sydney, undated (Box 12, Folder 134)
  - Levine, Abraham, undated (Box 12, Folder 135)
  - Levine, Jack L., undated (Box 12, Folder 136)
  - Levinson, Leon, undated (Box 12, Folder 137)
  - Lewis, William, Jr., undated (Box 12, Folder 138)
  - Lichtman, Paul, undated (Box 12, Folder 139)
  - Linden, Arthur, undated (Box 12, Folder 140)
  - Lipraan, Daniel, undated (Box 12, Folder 141)
  - Lipow, Eugene, undated (Box 12, Folder 142)
  - Liverett, Leon, undated (Box 12, Folder 143)
  - Lloyd, Alien, undated (Box 12, Folder 144)
  - Lloyd, Margaret, undated (Box 12, Folder 145)
  - Lockhart, Jean, undated (Box 12, Folder 146)
  - Loftus, James, undated (Box 12, Folder 147)
  - Long, Albert, undated (Box 12, Folder 148)
  - Long, James, undated (Box 12, Folder 149)
  - Lord, John, undated (Box 12, Folder 150)
  - Loube, Samuel, undated (Box 12, Folder 151)
  - Lourie, Reginald, undated (Box 12, Folder 152)
  - Louzan, John, undated (Box 12, Folder 153)
  - Love, James, undated (Box 12, Folder 154)
  - Lucas, Thomas, undated (Box 12, Folder 155)
  - Luckett, William, undated (Box 12, Folder 156)
  - Lumpkin, Martha, undated (Box 12, Folder 157)
  - Lyles, John, undated (Box 12, Folder 158)
  - Lynch, Daniel, undated (Box 12, Folder 159)
  - Lynch, John, undated (Box 12, Folder 160)
  - Lyons, James, undated (Box 12, Folder 161)
  - Lyons, Sidney, undated (Box 12, Folder 162)
  - Eanet, Morton Philip, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Ebert, Stanley, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Ecker, Lewis C., undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Edison, Thomas George, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Edwards, Clarence Carl, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Egan, John Robert, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Englehart Jr., Otto Theodore., undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Errgong, William H., undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Ewan, John Radcliffe, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Eanet, Paul, undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Ecker Henry D., undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Economos, George T., undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Eger, Alban, undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Ehrmantraut, Wilfred Russell, undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Eig, Blaine, undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Einstein, Hugo, undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Eisenberg, Herman, undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Eisenberg, Sanford, undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Engh, Otto Anderson, undated (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Epstein, Jerome H., undated (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Epstein, Julius, undated (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Etheridge, Clayton, undated (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Etienne, Wolcott Loweree, undated (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Evans, John M., undated (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Everding, Charles Jerome, undated (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Everett, John E., undated (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Farwell, Charles, undated (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Fishman, Samuel, undated (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Fitzgerald, James Edward, undated (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Fleury, George Jenkins, undated (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Flockes, Milton, undated (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Folston, Mortimer James, undated (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Forester, Charles, undated (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Foster, Stuart O., undated (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Fugitt, Elmer, Wink, undated (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Fusfeld, Cecile, undated (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Farrell, John A., undated (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Fazekas, Joseph Francis, undated (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Feffer, Henry, undated (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Feffer, James J., undated (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Ferguson, Edward E., undated (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Ferguson, William H., undated (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Feriozi, Dan John, undated (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Ferry, Alien Montague, undated (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Finck, Harold Y., undated (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Finegan, Eugene, undated (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Finnerty Jr., Frank A., undated (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Fischer, Richard H., undated (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Fisher, Gerald John, undated (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Fjordbotten, Alf Leee, undated (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Fleischer, Ronald, undated (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Fleischmann, Edna, undated (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Fogarty, Thomas Patrick, undated (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Foret, Marcel J., undated (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - Fowler, Richard C., undated (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Fox, Mary Alice, undated (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Fox III, Samuel M., undated (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - Fraga, Juan Reynaldo, undated (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - Frank, William, undated (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - Frank, Randolph, undated (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - Franks, Maurice, undated (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - Fraser, Clarence Kendall, undated (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - Frey, Cornelius Paul, undated (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - Friedel, Herbert Jack, undated (Box 13, Folder 64)
  - Friedenberg, Harry, undated (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - Friedman, Joseph M., undated (Box 13, Folder 66)
  - Gadol, William Norman, undated (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - Cannon Jr., James A., undated (Box 13, Folder 68)
  - Gartland, George, undated (Box 13, Folder 69)
  - Gee, George L., Jr., undated (Box 13, Folder 70)
  - Geist, Jack Emil, undated (Box 13, Folder 71)
  - Gelmi, Ottavio, undated (Box 13, Folder 72)
  - Gerwig, Walter Henry, undated (Box 13, Folder 73)
  - Gilbert, Jules, undated (Box 13, Folder 74)
  - Gilday, Thomas Aquinas, undated (Box 13, Folder 75)
  - Giles, Julian Westly, undated (Box 13, Folder 76)
  - Gilligan, John H., undated (Box 13, Folder 77)
  - Glatt, Milton Sandford, undated (Box 13, Folder 78)
  - Glover, Milton W., undated (Box 13, Folder 79)
  - Gold, Gustave Lennard, undated (Box 13, Folder 80)
  - Goldstein, Lloyd, undated (Box 13, Folder 81)
  - Goldstein, Joseph, undated (Box 13, Folder 82)
  - Gondos, Zoltan, undated (Box 13, Folder 83)
  - Goodman, Reuben, undated (Box 13, Folder 84)
  - Goodson, James Roy, undated (Box 13, Folder 85)
  - Gordon, Leon Stuart, undated (Box 13, Folder 86)
  - Gorsuch, Thomas Leonard, undated (Box 13, Folder 87)
  - Gould, Stanley, undated (Box 13, Folder 88)
  - Grassgreen, Irwin M., undated (Box 13, Folder 89)
  - Green, Stanley, undated (Box 13, Folder 90)
  - Griffin, Thomas E., undated (Box 13, Folder 91)
  - Grover, Harle Burton, undated (Box 13, Folder 92)
  - Guarino, George B., undated (Box 13, Folder 93)
  - Gudbrandson, Bjorn, undated (Box 13, Folder 94)
  - Guerrero, Efrain, undated (Box 13, Folder 95)
  - Gurwin, Bernard, undated (Box 13, Folder 96)
  - Guynn, Ray Frederick, undated (Box 13, Folder 97)
  - Gant, Landen G., undated (Box 13, Folder 98)
  - Garza, Santiago, undated (Box 13, Folder 99)
  - Gates, Herbert, undated (Box 13, Folder 100)
  - Gay, Claudine Moss, undated (Box 13, Folder 101)
  - Gay, Lendall C., undated (Box 13, Folder 102)
  - Geier, Fred A.J., undated (Box 13, Folder 103)
  - Geiger, Jason, undated (Box 13, Folder 104)
  - Gerber, Leon, undated (Box 13, Folder 105)
  - Gibb Jr., William Travis, undated (Box 13, Folder 106)
  - Gibson Jr., Frank E., undated (Box 13, Folder 107)
  - Giffin, Edgar D., undated (Box 13, Folder 108)
  - Gill Jr., William T., undated (Box 13, Folder 109)
  - Gill, Fred A., undated (Box 13, Folder 110)
  - Gill, Dorothy, undated (Box 13, Folder 111)
  - Gladsden, Eugene S., undated (Box 13, Folder 112)
  - Glew, Donald Jr., undated (Box 13, Folder 113)
  - Glick, Herbert D., undated (Box 13, Folder 114)
  - Goffredi, Louis J., undated (Box 13, Folder 115)
  - Goldberg, Herbert A., undated (Box 13, Folder 116)
  - Golden, Benjamin, undated (Box 13, Folder 117)
  - Goldman, Milton L., undated (Box 13, Folder 118)
  - Goldman, Ralph, undated (Box 13, Folder 119)
  - Goldstein, Louis, undated (Box 13, Folder 120)
  - Combos, Ervin Alexander, undated (Box 13, Folder 121)
  - Gonder, Thomas A., undated (Box 13, Folder 122)
  - Gordon, Armand B., undated (Box 13, Folder 123)
  - Gordon, Everett J., undated (Box 13, Folder 124)
  - Gordon, Stanley J., undated (Box 13, Folder 125)
  - Gordon, Samuel Chrabolovjski, undated (Box 13, Folder 126)
  - Gordon, David Stuart, undated (Box 13, Folder 127)
  - Gossels, Conrad L., undated (Box 13, Folder 128)
  - Gould, Ernest, undated (Box 13, Folder 129)
  - Gould, Arnold H., undated (Box 13, Folder 130)
  - Goumas, Marcus Peter, undated (Box 13, Folder 131)
  - Grant, James Q., undated (Box 13, Folder 132)
  - Gray, George A., Jr., undated (Box 13, Folder 133)
  - Gray, Paul H., undated (Box 13, Folder 134)
  - Greenbaum, Seymour, undated (Box 13, Folder 135)
  - Greenberg, Robert, undated (Box 13, Folder 136)
  - Greenberg, Arnold S., undated (Box 13, Folder 137)
  - Greenberg, Milton M., undated (Box 13, Folder 138)
  - Greenfield, Albert A., undated (Box 13, Folder 139)
  - Greenlaw, Joseph James, undated (Box 13, Folder 140)
  - Grennan, Arthur, undated (Box 13, Folder 141)
  - Groh, Robert H., undated (Box 13, Folder 142)
  - Groilman, Jaye Jacob, undated (Box 13, Folder 143)
  - Gruver, Clifton Rhodes, undated (Box 13, Folder 144)
  - Gruverm, Robert H., undated (Box 13, Folder 145)
  - Guy, Richard, undated (Box 13, Folder 146)
  - Hall, Allan, undated (Box 13, Folder 147)
  - Hall, Edwin Presley, undated (Box 13, Folder 148)
  - Hall, Winston Conwell, undated (Box 13, Folder 149)
  - Hand, John Phelps, jr., undated (Box 13, Folder 150)
  - Hanna, William Henry, undated (Box 13, Folder 151)
  - Harmon, Ernest Emery, undated (Box 13, Folder 152)
  - Hawfield, James, undated (Box 13, Folder 153)
  - Hawkins, Robert C., Jr., undated (Box 13, Folder 154)
  - Heffner, William Nason, undated (Box 13, Folder 155)
  - Heller, Paul, undated (Box 13, Folder 156)
  - Hendricks, Franklin D., undated (Box 13, Folder 157)
  - Hertz, Roy, undated (Box 13, Folder 158)
  - Herz, Elisabeth Kremenak, undated (Box 13, Folder 159)